When you run meshclickdraw.exe after building, you will see the 3 control pts that are fixed.
User will need to input the middle two points which make up the arcs, after they are both clicked, the arcs will appear.
User also can't input points within 1 of the fixed control points (is 1 too small for an invalid point?)
User can press R or Enter to redo/confirm, respectively.
Some print statements for directing the user are written to the terminal while running exe

